But you're willing to tank it if it's not?
They are willing to tank it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, sorry.
That is exactly the problem, is when the media reports this as not their fault.
And I'm just going to say, I know so many of you, I have so much respect for what you do,
but let's tell the truth here.
We are not tanking anything.
The debt ceiling has been raised because we have an appropriations process,
and during the appropriations process, the budget process, we negotiate.
The Republicans can try to get whatever they can there, but then we agree.
Now, this is important. The American people should hear this.
Then we agree on spending.
Republicans agree. Democrats agree.
We decide, we appropriate money based on what Congress has passed,
legislation that we pass in this body.
That is democracy.
And then, when it's time, the debt ceiling is raised to accommodate what we have already passed,
Republicans and Democrats, in a democratic process.
I'm sorry, let me just clarify.
Okay.
I'm sorry.